

LAUTARO EPIFANI

Full-Stack Developer

+34 651 68 67 18

epifanilautaro@gmail.com

Portfolio

Barcelona, Spain

in <u>Linkedin</u>

Github

About me

Il find myself working on proyects every day to progress in applitacion development with Javascript (React) & Node. I usually use Typescript, Redux along side with React-testing-library & Jest. I focus on improving the structure and scalability of my projects. I have experience with the stack MERN & deployments in Aws S3 and Lambda.

Technologies

Html Css

JavaScript

React Js

Node Js

Typescript

Next Js

MySql

PHP

Languages

English B2

Spanish native

Experience

O May 2023 - Present

Oxygen Academy & Recruiting

Full-stack web Developer

Development of the Hotel Miranda project:

-Design, layout and functionality of the web: HTML, CSS (SASS), BEM methodology and Javascript. <u>Hotel Miranda Link</u>.

React application of the hotel administration Dashboard.

-Design and layout: Styled Components. Functionalities and state management: Redux. Typescript. Testing: Jest & React Testing Library, Cypress. Login authentication with jwtoken. Manipulate data tables in mysql or mongoDb through an express server and connect to the front end via redux async thunks. <u>Dashboard Link</u>.

October 2022- March 2023

Freelance

Web Developer

-Store Web Proyect: Interactive web applitaction with product rating system with dynamic graph that is updated after each user rating. https://testveggipedia.firebaseapp.com

-Refactor code, add React Js components. Add (buttons, media files, texts) in Sanity CDN for better user experience. Make web responsive and styling with Tailwind Css.. https://www.lumoview.com

Education

O Training React

Oxygen Academy & Recruiting

Apr 2023 - May 2023

OxygenShop application. HTML CSS SASS Javascript and responsive app. <u>Oxygen Shop Link</u>.

Photos App. Figma design. Redux template. using the Unsplash Api. <u>Photos App Link</u>.

O Certificate React Js Course

It Academy, Barcelona Activa

October 2022 - January 2023

Final Project: React Router, Context, Typescript. Firebase for autentication and data storage including image. firebase hosting. Styles with Tailwind css.

O JavaScript Course

National Technological University, Buenos Aires November 2019 - February 2020

Final project simple web page with Html, Css and pure JavaScript functions